http://www.powerserviceinc.com/en/privacy-notice

Paint & Coatings
Pipe, Valves & Fittings (PVF)
Engineering and Application
Artificial LiftElectricalPumpsTotal Valve SolutionsTurnkey Fabrication & Packages
Supply Chain Solutions
Manufacturing ServicesMaterial Assets & Inventory ManagementSourcing & Procurement
Digital Solutions
DistributionNOW is committed to providing world-class technology for ecommerce, data, and supply chain efficiency, all powered by DigitalNOW, our expanding platform of digital solutions. Get the products and information you need, when you need it, from the comfort and convenience of your PC or mobile device.
View More
Industry Applications
Energy
Downstream (coming soon)MidstreamUpstream Artificial LiftUpstream Offshore Drilling Upstream Onshore DrillingUpstream Offshore Production Facilities (coming soon)Upstream Onshore Production Facilities
Mining & Minerals (coming soon)
Energy
DNOW stands ready to serve customers in every step of the energy value chain. Our expertise spans the upstream, midstream and downstream segments so that your operation doesn't skip a beat.
View More
About
Affiliated Brands
Dura ProductsLight & Energy DistributionMacLean ElectricalOdessa PumpsPower ServiceTS&M SupplyTS&M Supply Fiberglass
Careers
Hiring EventsInternship ProgramSales & Operations Rotational Program
Corporate Citizenship
Corporate Compliance StatementsCorporate SustainabilityDiversity
News and Events
Company NewsEvents
Why DNOW
Case StudiesFlexible Operating ModelQualityService Commitment
Resources
Investors
Analyst Coverage
Corporate Governance
ManagementBoard of DirectorsCommittee CompositionGovernance Hotline
Corporate Sustainability
Events and Presentations
Event CalendarPresentations
Financial Results
Investor Contact
Investors FAQs
Press Release
SEC Filings
Stock Information
MENU
DNOW Affiliated Brands
Power Service
Power Service
We are your one-stop solution for rotating and process equipment engineering, design, installation, fabrication, distribution and service. We’ve been serving the industry for more than six decades with high-tech solutions to complex industrial interests.
We're here to help.
Get In Touch With A Rotating and Process Equipment
Expert
About Power Service
Part of DNOW's U.S. Process Solutions division, Power Service leverages a total of 540,000 sq. ft. of fabrication and office facilities to provide our customers with a variety of process and production equipment for upstream and midstream oil and gas, as well as the downstream refining sector, mining, water transfer and water disposal (SWD) markets.
Our team of mechanical, petroleum and application engineers – along with our draftsman and sales staff – can design process and production solutions tailored exactly to your specifications.No job is too complicated, so whether you need custom water disposal/injection plants, chemical injection packages, LACT units, ASME vessels, two-phase or multiphase separators, or air compressor skids, Power Service can deliver the right solution to fit your needs.Our fabrication facilities are strategically located in the U.S. to service the downstream industrial Gulf Coast market, Texas, Oklahoma, New Mexico, Colorado, Wyoming, Montana and North and South Dakota.
Browse Power Service Products & Services
ASME Pressure Vessels
Engineering & Design Services
Gas Measurement
LACT Units
Launchers & Receivers
Process Equipment Field Services
Produced Water Transfer
Vapor Recovery Units (VRU)
Water Disposal & Waterflood
Air Compressors & Dryers
Blowers
Pumps
Our Suppliers
In-House Fabrication
From beginning to end, we can design, engineer and fabricate your projects in-house. We have more than 500,000 sq. ft. of shop space for world-class welding, assembly, inspection and painting, and our design and drafting department has a combined 20 years of experience in process design/drafting, fabrication and ASME code analysis.
Certifications
ABSA
ASME "U" Stamp
CE
CSA
CWB
NB
NBCA "R" Stamp
UL
Technical Resources
Find additional information on our technical capabilities, as well as brochures and datasheets on our rotating and process equipment.
See Our Resources
Power Service Locations
Casper Main Campus
5625 Chapman Place
Casper, WY 82604 USA
Phone: 800-743-4774
Frederick
8413 Rowe Place
Phone: 800-276-7175
Green River (Piping Specialties / Power Service)
68 Uinta Dr
Green River, WY 82935 USA
Phone: 877-562-7867
Contact UsDistributionNOW is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We will only use your personal information to administer your request. We will never sell your personal data to a third party or use the information you provide on this form for marketing purposes.
How can we help?*
Request Information
Request for Quote
Customer Support
Investor Relations
Supplier Inquiry
Other
First Name*
Comoros
Congo (Congo-Brazzaville)
Costa Rica
Côte d'Ivoire
Croatia
Cuba
Cyprus
Czech Republic
Democratic Republic of the Congo
Denmark
Luxembourg
Macedonia (FYROM)
Madagascar
Malawi
Malaysia
Maldives
Mali
Malta
Marshall Islands
Mauritania
Careers
Regional Pages (more coming soon)
Canada
Latin America
Follow Us
© Copyright 2020 DistributionNOW. All rights reserved.
Terms of Use
Privacy Notice
Cookie Notice
Shop Online
Acquisitions
Careers
Our Locations
Products & Services
Paint & Coatings
Pipe, Valves & Fittings (PVF)
Power Generation & Transmission
Process & Production Equipment
Pumps, Compressors & Packages
Safety & PPE
Tools & Welding Equipment
Solutions
Digital Solutions
Engineering and Application
Energy
Downstream (coming soon)
Midstream
Upstream Artificial Lift
Upstream Offshore Drilling
Upstream Onshore Drilling
Upstream Offshore Production Facilities (coming soon)
Upstream Onshore Production Facilities
Mining & Minerals (coming soon)
About
Affiliated Brands
Dura Products
Light & Energy Distribution
MacLean Electrical
Odessa Pumps
Power Service
TS&M Supply
Stock Information
In order to analyse site usage, to assist with marketing efforts, and to enable you to provide feedback, this site uses cookies (technology that remembers your use of the website by placing tracking tools on your device). DNOW L.P. and its affiliates, parents, and subsidiaries use cookies to store or access information on your device to monitor and better understand how visitors navigate the site and how they arrived. For more information, or to edit your preferences, click the “Cookie Settings” link to the right. Do you accept these cookies and the processing of your personal data involved? Your consent to our use of cookies will remain valid for 12 months. (Click here for more information)
Cookie Settings
Accept Cookies
Privacy Preference Center
×
Your Privacy
Essential Cookies
Performance Cookies
Functional Cookies
Third Party Cookies
Your Privacy
When you visit any web site, it may store or retrieve information on your browser, mostly in the form of cookies. This information might be about you, your preferences or your device and is mostly used to make the site work as you expect it to. The information does not usually directly identify you, but it can give you a more personalized web experience. Because we respect your right to privacy, you can choose not to allow some types of cookies. Click on the different category headings to find out more and change our default settings. However, blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience of the site and the services we are able to offer.
Essential Cookies
Essential cookies enable core functionality such as security, network management, and accessibility. These cookies are necessary for our website to function properly and cannot be switched off or our website will not work properly with your device. For more information on how these cookies work, please see our ''Cookie Notice
page'.
Performance Cookies
These cookies allow us to measure and improve the performance of our website by by collecting and reporting information such as the number of visits, return visits and the pages that are most visited. The cookies collect information in a way that does not directly identify anyone. For more information on how these cookies work, please see our ''Cookie Notice
page'.
Allow performance cookies
Functional Cookies
These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalization. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages. If you do not allow these cookies, then some or all of these services may not function properly. For more information on how these cookies work, please see our ''Cookie Notice
page'.
Allow functional cookies
Third Party Cookies
These cookies are set by third parties to collect personal data about you to provide personalized advertisements and to provide analytics on the website. For more information on how these cookies work, please see our ''Cookie Notice
page'.
Allow third party cookies
Allow All
Save Settings
